《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24.
沃克探员告诉我还有希望
Agent Walker told me that there's a chance,
有一线希望  我可能救得了你
A small chance that I could help you.
我快死了
I'm dying.
即便有能让我幸存的一线生机
And whatever small chance there is to stop that from happening
我也决不愿承受  让你坐在我身边
It is not worth the pain for me to let you
看我死去时的那种切肤之痛
Sit there and watch me die.
爸  我不想失去你
Daddy, I don't want to lose you.
过来
Come here.
我不想失去你
I don't.
怎么了
What is it?
宝贝  抱歉
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
可你得走了
But you need to go.
霍奇斯是今天所有事件的主谋
Hodges was behind everything that happened today,
从飞机的失事
From the planes going down
-一直到袭击白宫  -什么
- To the attack on the white house. - What?
他还该为我弟弟的死负责
He's also responsible for the death of my brother.
你要知道的就是霍奇斯拿到了协议
All you need to know is Hodges worked a deal.
证人保护协议  我母亲批准了
Witness protection. My mother approved it
然后他就会逍遥法外  除非有人出面干涉
And he's going free... unless someone intervenes.
我会给你联系方式  价钱
I'll get you contact information, a price
还有你如何转账的说明
And instructions on how to transfer the funds.
马丁  我是奥利维亚·泰勒
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor.
我跟你找的人谈过了
I spoke to the contact,
但没有谈成
But I couldn't go through with it.
吉布安  听我说
Listen to me, Jibraan.
如果你不照我说的做
If you don't do exactly as I say,
你会眼睁睁看着你弟弟死在你面前
You're going to watch your younger brother die right in front of your eyes.
然后
And then...
我也会杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
我们的父母死在美国人手上  哈米德
It was the Americans who killed our parents, Hamid.
我要让他们血债血偿
I'm going to make them pay.
你对我哥做了什么
What have you done to my brother?
你给他洗脑了吗  这根本就不是我哥
You've poisoned his mind! This isn't my brother!
我们在找一个在这里朝拜的人
We're looking for a man who worships here.
他叫吉布安·阿尔扎利安  你认识他吗
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian. Do you know him?
我认识他  但他不是恐怖分子
I know him, but he is not a terrorist.
我们来不是要和你争论这个问题
We did not come here to debate this with you!
他住在哪里
Where does he live?!
你带着莫须有的消息
You come into a house of worship
闯入我的礼拜堂
With information you should not have,
肆无忌惮的指控
An outrageous accusation,
没有合法的搜查令  还威胁我
No legal warrant and threaten me.
我没有威胁你
I have not threatened you.
暂时还没
Not yet.
但我们都知道接下来会发生什么
But we both know where this is going.
杰克  我是克罗伊  我发现
Jack, it's Chloe. I found something weird
吉布安·阿尔扎利安的事有些蹊跷
About these hits on Jibraan Al-zarian.
我告诉过你他的账户
You know how I said that the $2 million
在6个月内总共存入了2百万美元
Was deposited into his account over a period of six months?
那不对  时间被提前了
Well, that wasn't right. They were backdated.
他浏览过的那些极端分子网站呢
What about the extremist web sites he was visiting?
时间标记也是一样的情况
Same thing with the time stamps.
网站访问时间是30分钟前被篡改提前的
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
吉布安很可能是无辜的
Jibraan could be innocent.
什么情况  探员
What do you have, agent?
武装分子在里屋  持有一名人质
Armed hostile in the back room holding a hostage.
有阿尔梅达的消息吗
What about Almeida?
他不在里面  自己看吧
He's not in there. see for yourself.
不是
No.
那是吉布安的弟弟  哈米德
That's Jibraan's brother, Hamid.
他们以他来要挟  让吉布安唯命是从
They're using him as leverage to make Jibraan do what they want.
你怎么那么肯定
How can you be sure?
因为若是我也会这么干
Because that's what I would have done.
哈米德  住手
Hamid, stop!
把玻璃放下
Put it down.
我们是联邦调查局  我们需要留活口
We're FBI. We need him alive.
以下情节发生在凌晨5点至6点间
The following takes place between 5 a.m. and 6 a.m.
正改装毒气罐以扩大杀伤范围
The canister's being retrofitted to maximize dispersion.
我们计划一小时内
We're on target to release the bioweapon
在华盛顿中央车站释放毒气
At Washington Central Station within the hour.
你估计的伤亡数准确吗
Your casualty estimates are holding up?
只是保守数字
I think they're conservative.
很大一部分病原体
A significant portion of the pathogen will escape
会进入到车站通风系统
Into the station's ventilation system,
再传播到别处
Which will circulate it for us.
8千至1万名乘客会暴露在毒气中
Between 8,000 and 10,000 commuters will be exposed.
给我说说阿尔扎利安先生的情况
Tell me about Mr. Al-zarian.
他听话吗
Is he compliant?
是的  他目前最关心的是他弟弟的安危
Yes. His primary concern at this point is for the safety of his brother.
很好
All right.
关于这次计划他知道多少
What's his level of awareness regarding the plan?
要到回天无力的地步他才会知道
He won't know anything about the canister until it's too late.
很好  事成之后我们再谈
Good. We'll talk once it's done.
启动装置运转正常
Trigger mechanism's working.
这个装置会随时跟踪你的位置
This device will tell me where you are at all times.
我们还可以通过它交谈
It will also allow us to talk to each other.
谈什么
Talk about what?
你还没有告诉我到底要我做什么
You still haven't told me what you want me to do.
现在我只想让你搭地铁
Right now I just want you to get on the subway
搭乘红线列车坐到华盛顿中心
And take the Red Line all the way to Washington Center.
我到那以后呢
And when I get there?
到时你就知道了
I'll let you know then.
我不傻
I'm not stupid.
我知道你这么做是想让我背黑锅
I know you are going to blame me for something.
-吉布安  -你想做什么
- Jibraan... - What's your plan, huh?
你要伤害平民吗
You are going to hurt people?
吉布安  你现在唯一要担心的
Jibraan, the only person you need to worry about right now
是你弟弟
Is your brother.
你照我说的做  哈米德就不会死
You follow my instructions, and hamid lives.
你要是做傻事  他会死得很难看
You do something stupid, and he dies... badly.
明白了吗
Understood?
明白
Good.
坐红线列车一路向西
Red line, westbound,
到华盛顿中心  听懂了吗
To washington center, got it?
走了  快点
Let's go. come on.
很抱歉发生这样的事
Sorry this had to happen like this.
我们会找到你哥哥的
We will find your brother.
你该跟他谈谈
You should talk to him.
这孩子什么都不知道
Kid doesn't know anything,
只知道他哥是在半小时前被托尼带走的
Except that his brother was taken by Tony about a half an hour ago.
他也没听到关于袭击目标和时间的话
He didn't overhear anything about a target or the time frame.
目前他是我们唯一的线索
Right now, he's our only lead.
他伤得很重
He's badly injured.
-我不知道他能不能开口  -老天啊
- I don't know if he's in any condition to talk. - My god!
按着他的头  我要给他打点吗啡
Hold his head. I'm going to give him some morphine.
你不能给他打
No, you're not.
他的伤口在神经密布区
His wound is in the middle of a nerve cluster.
-他会痛得休克的  -我知道
- He can go into shock from the pain. - I know.
让开
Back off.
我要你去屋外边
I want you to step out of the room.
交给你了
Do what you need to do.
阿尔梅达在哪里
Where's Almeida?
求你了  给我打点吗啡吧
Please, just give me the morphine.
你老实交代  就给你吗啡
I'll give you the morphine as soon as you talk.
托尼·阿尔梅达在哪
Where's Tony Almeida?
袭击目标是什么
What's the target?
我不知道
I don't know...
-袭击目标是什么  -我不知道
- What's the target?! - I don't know!
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth!
我的任务只是看着这小子监控这里的情况
My job was just to watch the kid and monitor things here.
阿尔梅达没告诉我
Almeida didn't tell me
他要去哪里或者袭击目标在哪里
Where he was going or where the target is.
你怎么跟他联系
How do you contact him?
我不能说
I can't.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
我有一个号码
I have a number.
但只有紧急情况的时候我才能打
But I'm not supposed to use it unless there's a problem.
你最好赶快编一个出来
You better start thinking of one fast.
他电话在哪里
Where is his phone?
在这
I have it here.
给他打够量的吗啡  让他说话时不露马脚
Give him enough morphine so that he can take the pain out of his voice.
除此之外  别打多了
Nothing more.
你让克罗伊追踪这个号码
I want you to get Chloe to run a trace on this number.
叫她把追踪信息反馈到我们手机上
Tell her to feed it back to our cell phones.
你最好赶快想想要说什么
You better start thinking about what you're going to say.
你要是敢耍花招
You try and screw with me on this,
这将是你这辈子做的最后一件事了  明白没
It'll be the last thing you ever do. You understand me?
明白了吗
Do you understand me?
是的
Yes.
詹尼斯·古德
Janis Gold.
我是蕾妮
It's Renee.
让克罗伊对一个全球移动通信系统序列号
I need Chloe to run a peer-to-peer cellular trace
-做个点对点的手机追踪  -我能做的
- From a GSM ID. - I can do that.
杰克要求克罗伊来做这个
Jack asked for Chloe to run point on this.
号码是多少
What's the number?
-A  C  3316  -收到
- Alpha-Charlie-3316. - Got it.
-你直接把结果传给我和杰克  -稍等
- I'll need you to run it back through to me and jack. - Hold on.
-她正在做  -很好
- She's working on it. - Good.
我来建立一个当地的协议
I'll open up the locate protocol.
你去建一个安全的虚拟专用网络
You establish a secure VPN.
好的  在卫星一号线路上开启
All right, opening a channel on the inter-sat...
为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
怎么了
What?
你知道通过直接内存存储连接节点更快的
You know connecting through a DMA node would be a lot faster.
我不知道用直接内存节点读取会更快
No, I don't know it's quicker to use a DMA node
否则刚才我就那么做了
Or else I would have done just that.
我不知道直接内存存储节点上传运行中
I had no idea the DMA nodes were up and running.
是吗  因为这个已经上传运行了两年多
Really? Because they've been up and running for about two years.
听起来显然我不可能
It's obvious sound that I'll never be able to do things
像你在反恐小组那样工作出色
As well as you did at CTU.
我只要求在你指出这点的时候
All I ask is that you not make me feel like an idiot
不用让我感觉像个白痴
While you're pointing that out.
好吧
All right.
沃克探员  追踪连接建立了　正在运行
Agent Walker, the trace is up and running
你们准备好就随时工作
Whenever you're ready.
-杰克  -克罗伊  我接通了
- Jack. - Chloe, I'm on.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
号码是多少
What's the number?
202  555
202... 555...
0147.
正在呼叫
It's ringing.
你怎么打电话给我
Why are you calling me?
我正在检查阿尔扎利安的电脑
I was checking Al-Zarian's computer,
仔细检查我们输入的所有东西
Double-checking everything we planted.
-然后呢  -我们在瑞士开的银行刚给他发邮件
- And? - The bank that we use in Switzerland just e-mailed him,
说拒绝了一项阿尔扎利安的转账
Rejecting one of the transfers we made in Al-zarian's name.
你应该知道怎么重新提交申请吧
You know how to resubmit it?
我不太确定
I'm not sure.
你看到这个了吗
Are you getting this?
托尼在他手机里装了什么东西
Tony's got something on his phone that's
用来加密他的位置  我正在想办法
Encrypting his location. I'm trying to get around it.
好吧
All right.
打电话给我们苏黎世的人
Call our man in Zurich.
他会帮你搞定
He'll walk you through it.
好的  我只想在打电话之前
All right. I just wanted
得到你的授权
To get your authorization before I did that.
还有别的问题吗
Any other problems?
没了
No.
很好
Good.
克罗伊  你查到地址了吗
Chloe, did you get that?
我没有足够时间来解密所有的地址数据
I didn't have time to decrypt all the location data.
现在就查到他在
All I know right now
亚当-摩根区的某个地方
Is that he's somewhere in the Adams Morgan district.
我们时间所剩无几
We're running out of time.
我们得把那个范围缩小
We're going to have to narrow that down.
我正在努力  我得解密其他的地址数据
I'm trying. I have to decrypt the rest of the location data.
-那得多长时间  -不知道
- How long is that going to take? - I don't know.
见鬼  克罗伊  我们得抓紧时间
Damn it, chloe, we've got to do better than that.
我要挂电话了
I need to get off the phone.
詹尼斯  我要你联系首都警察
Janis, I want you to contact metro P.D.
我要你指挥他们的危险品应急小队
I want you to get them to move their hazmat teams
和战术小队到亚当摩根区去
And their tactical teams over to Adams Morgan.
我们正在路上  我们走
We're on our way now. Let's go.
首都旅客们  这周末
Metro passengers, this weekend
将没有蓝线特快列车
There will be no Blue Line express service
开往阿灵顿和麦克林
To Arlington and Mcclean.
特快列车将于星期一重新启动
Express service will be resumed on Monday.
我要你打电话通知警察
I need you to call the police.
您说什么
Excuse me?
请大声点  先生
Speak up, sir.
我不能
I can't do that.
他们在监听
They're listening.
谁在监听
Who's listening?
那些抓了我弟弟的人
The people who have my brother.
恐怖分子
The terrorists.
他们会杀了我弟弟的
They're going to kill my brother
除非我按他们说的做
Unless I do what they say.
他们要我登上这趟列车
They want me to get on this train.
就这些吗
That's it?
-就登上这列车吗  -是的  求你了
- Just get on the train? - Yes, please.
你得帮帮我  好吗
You have to help me, okay?
你得打电话通知警察
You have to call the police.
有什么问题吗  先生
Is there a problem here, sir?
是的  谢谢你  警官
Yes, yes, thank you, officer.
求求你  我需要你的帮忙
Please, I need your help.
先生  请冷静点  这边来
Sir, just calm down and step this way.
什么事
What is it?
他们抓了我的弟弟
Listen, they have my brother hostage.
你必须相信我
Okay, you have to believe me!
把耳机放回去
Put the earpiece back in.
什么
What?
我说  把耳机放回去
I said, put the earpiece back in.
快
Now.
听着  吉布安
Listen, Jibraan,
我很理解你迫不得已铤而走险
I understand you had to try.
但别再那么做了
But don't do it again.
你弟弟的命在你手里
Your brother's life depends on it.
好的  求你了  别伤害我弟弟
Yes, okay, please, okay, just don't hurt him, okay?
那就得看你表现了
Well, that's up to you.
我会照你吩咐去做的
Yes, I'll do whatever you say, okay?
我不会惹任何麻烦的
I won't cause any more problems.
我发誓
I promise.
好吧
All right.
你还记得给你的指示吗
Do you remember your instructions?
是的
Yes, uh...
乘西行红线列车到华盛顿中心站
Westbound Red Line to Washington center.
我们会监视你的
We'll be watching.
一直监视着
We're always watching.
喂
Hello?
泰勒小姐  我是皮尔斯探员
Ms. Taylor, this is agent pierce.
什么事  亚伦
Yes, Aaron?
伍兹部长想要见您
Secretary Woods was asking for you.
您告诉我说回官邸休息了
You told me you were retiring to the residence,
但楼上的情况显示
But upstairs detail confirmed
您不在那里
That you're not there.
蒂姆为什么要见我
Why is Tim looking for me?
司法部正在调查乔纳斯·霍格斯
The justice department is investigating
的汽车炸弹的事
The Jonas Hodges car bombing.
他们要求查看电话和互联网记录
They're requesting phone and internet records
而且他们要询问每个人
And want to interview everyone, as well.
我不知道司法部也介入了
I didn't realize justice was getting involved.
很显然  只有11个人
Apparently, there were only 11 people
知道霍格斯还活着
Who knew Hodges was alive.
显然这消息是有人故意泄露的
It stands to reason that information was leaked.
好吧  我会尽快回去的
Okay, I'll get there as soon as I can.
您在哪里
Where are you?
我有件私人事情要办
I needed to run a personal errand.
阁下  我能把这理解成
Ma'am, am I to understand
您已经离开了白宫范围
That you've left the white house premises
而且没有特工的保护吗
Without secret service protection?
亚伦  我不会花太久的
I won't be long, Aaron.
就10分钟
Ten minutes.
泰勒小姐
Ms. Taylor,
这个很严肃地违反了协议
This is a serious breach of protocol.
您的安全就是我的职责
Your safety is my responsibility.
亚伦  我明白
Aaron, I know.
我答应你没有下次了
I promise you it won't happen again.
仅仅替我掩护一下到我回去
Just cover for me till I get back?
你能帮我吗  亚伦
Will you do that for me, Aaron?
是的  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是个错误  马丁  我们不该见面的
This is a mistake, Martin. We shouldn't be meeting.
你需要冷静下来  奥利维亚
Okay, you need to calm down, Olivia.
我需要见到你  电话里你都歇底斯里了
I needed to see you; you were hysterical on the phone.
你不明白  现在都有调查了
No, you don't understand! There's an investigation.
司法部都在询问我在哪了
Look, the justice department is asking about my whereabouts!
你以为当政府证人被谋杀的时候
Okay, did you think no one would bat an eye
没人会被调查吗
When a government witness was murdered?
我告诉过你我改变主意了
I told you I changed my mind.
我没有转账
I didn't transfer the funds.
你让我联系的那个人说
The man you put me in touch with said
不收到钱他不会动手
He wouldn't act until he received payment.
如果没人给他酬劳
Why would he go ahead and kill Hodges
他为什么还是下手干掉了霍奇斯呢
If he wasn't paid?
因为是我给他下的令
Because I told him to.
什么
What?
他打电话给我说
He called me and told me
钱还没到账
The money hadn't come through yet.
我告诉他你是懂规矩的  让他下手
I told him you were good for it and to proceed.
为什么  马丁  为什么这么做
Why, Martin? why would you do that?
霍奇斯马上就要进入证人保护计划
Hodges was going into Witness Protection,
这是最后下手的机会
There was a finite window of opportunity.
况且这正合你意啊
And because it's what you wanted.
对吧
Right?
尽管我再三警告你要三思
Despite all my warnings for you to reconsider,
你还是直视着我的眼睛
You looked me straight in the eye
告诉我你要霍奇斯死  非死不可
And you said you wanted Hodges dead, to make it happen.
我按你的意思做了  现在你梦想成真了
And I did, and he's dead.
天哪
Oh, my god...
可我的通话记录
But my phone records...
-电脑使用记录全都没清除   - 别操心
- M-my computer... everything...   - Don't worry about any of those.
我会给你传个程序  删除网页使用痕迹
I'll send you a program to erase your internet tracks.
你给我打的电话不会引起怀疑
The calls to me mean nothing.
奥利维亚  在你付诸行动之后
Olivia, the time to worry about your conscience
就没有良心谴责的后悔药可吃了
Was before you put this in motion.
如果你让这种不安控制了你
If you let this eat away at you,
别人就会注意到你的反常  并产生怀疑
People are going to notice and get suspicious.
你会把我们两个都拖下水
You will bring us both down...
还会殃及到你的母亲和她的政府
Destroy your mother and her administration.
想清楚  这是你想要的结果吗
Think about it. Is that what you want?
不是
No.
好  那就振作精神
Okay, then pull yourself together.
我答应你  你要是照我的话做
I promise you, this will all pass
我们都会相安无事
If you do what I say.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
说
Say it.
我能做到
I can do it.
奥利维亚  你得先把钱汇过去
You need to transfer the funds, Olivia.
别让这个家伙对你不满
You do not want this man unhappy with you.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
抱歉把你吵醒了
Sorry I woke you.
不不不  没关系
No, no, no, that's okay.
我被泰莉吵醒好多回了
I've been up with Teri a couple times anyway.
她一晚上都不得安宁
She's been having a rough night.
她应该是想妈妈了
I think she misses her mother.
听着
Oh, well, listen,
我打电话来是告诉你我的航班晚点了
I just called to let you know that my flight's been delayed.
好  晚了多久
Yeah, how long?
机场人员说是一个小时
Well, they're saying an hour.
实际可能晚点两个小时
Which probably means two.
好
Okay.
怎么了
What?
不知道  也许你该把这视为一种天意
I don't know, maybe you should see this as a sign.
天意
A sign?
暗示你该留在那里  努力说服你父亲
That you should stay there-- try to convince your father
就算他时日不多
That, uh, he should be spending whatever time
他也该和他的独生女一起度过
He has left with his only daughter.
尽管我很想陪他
As much as I want to,
他还是把话说得很清楚
He made it very clear
他不想让我陪在他身边看他死去
That he does not want me around to watch him die.
好吧
Okay, all right.
抱歉我谈起了令你不快的话题
Sorry I brought it up.
我和泰莉会去机场接你
Teri and I will be at the airport to pick you up.
我手机电量不足了
My battery is dying.
医院那边没意见吗
Is the hospital okay with that?
没  我和凯文谈过了
Yeah, I talked to Kevin.
他说会找人替我
He said he'd cover my rounds.
那真是  太好了
Well, that's-that's... that's great.
我等不及要见到你们了
Well, I can't wait to see you guys.
我爱你
I love you.
好  再见
Okay, bye.
莎拉  登机证呢
Sara, where are the boarding passes?
我看到你放进大衣口袋了  亲爱的
I saw you put them in your coat, honey.
抱歉  对不起
Oh, excuse me, sorry.
-没事  -抱歉
- That's all right. -Sorry.
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事  抱歉
Yeah, yeah, sorry.
L大街站到了
This stop, L  street.
This stop, L street.
下一站  华盛顿中心
Next stop is Washington Center.
下一站是终点站  华盛顿中心
Next stop is the last. Next stop is Washington center.
炸弹已经安放好
The package is in place.
释放装置既定扩散时间是
The dispersal mechanism is set to go off while
列车在华盛顿中心靠站时
The train is stopped at washington center.
好  我们在路上了
Good, we're on the move.
我们会在22大街接你
I'll pick you up at 22nd.
杰克  我破解了托尼的定位数据
Jack, I unlocked Tony's location data.
他在哪里  离这里三个街区
Where is he? Three blocks
马上就到22大街山你所在位置的南侧
Immediately south of your position on 22nd.
具体位置呢
Where exactly on 22nd?
就在你即将到达的街区西侧
West side of the block you're coming up on.
前方900英尺
900 feet ahead of you...
还有800英尺
800 feet...
所有小队  从南侧集结  准备行动
All teams, bring your units up from the south and prepare to move in.
好  我们看到他了
Okay, we've got him.
疑犯在一辆黑色货车里
Suspect is in a black van.
我们不能让这次行动演变为追捕行动
We can't let this turn into a pursuit.
坐稳
Hold on.
Hold on!
准备好了吗
Ready?
我抓到托尼的时候
Tony was trying to destroy
他正试图摧毁某种装置
Some kind of device when I grabbed him!
找到了
I got it!
把这垃圾押起来
Lock down this piece of crap.
什么装置
What do you got?
一种移动电脑  但几乎全被他破坏了
Some kind of mobile computer, but he damaged it pretty badly.
这电脑和这次恐怖袭击一定有关
This has got something to do with the attack.
联系克罗伊  看有什么发现
Contact Chloe, see what we can find.
我要搜查这辆货车   看有没有毒气罐
I'm gonna sweep the van for the canister.
托尼的超便携移动电脑已经全部损坏
Tony's UMPC device is damaged everywhere I look.
没有方法可以恢复原样  并正常运行
I don't think there's a way to get it back up and running.
那就试试恢复部分数据
Well, then try a partial reconstruct.
看看有没有托尼阴谋诡计的蛛丝马迹
Anything that can help us find out what Tony's been up to.
就现在的情况看  我不知道
At this point I don't even know
能否恢复数据
About our chances of even doing that.
-克罗伊  -我知道
- Chloe. - I know.
帮个忙　　把你的桌面镜像同步传给我
Do me a favor. send me your screen.
-为什么  -没什么为什么
- Why? - Why not?
怎么
What?
看来我能修复超便携移动电脑
Looks like I can reconstruct the memory state
被破坏时的内存数据
of the UMPC at the time it was damaged.
不行  里面完好无损的数据不够
No. there isn't enough intact data.
不  只读存储器模块里有
Yeah, there is, in the prom module.
许多掌上设备都在那备份了内存数据
A lot of handheld devices back up their memory state there.
这不可能修复
That can't be done,
-没有文件头就不行  -真的吗
- Not without the file headers. - Really?
鲍尔先生  阿尔梅达恢复意识了
Mr. bauer, Almeida just regained consciousness.
谢谢  别走开
Thank you. stay with this.
请你们回避
I need you to walk away.
拜托  你和你的手下请回避
Please, you and your men just walk away.
在哪里
Where is it?
毒气罐在哪里
Where's the canister?
你不告诉我  我不会停手
I am not going to stop until you tell me where it is.
为什么背叛我
Why did you betray me?
为什么
Why?
我已一无所有
I have nothing left to lose.
你快告诉我毒气罐的位置  要不然
You either tell me where that canister is, or so help me god,
我现在就把你就地正法
I will lay you down right here, right now.
你觉得我还有什么可以失去呢  杰克
You think I've got anything left to lose, Jack?
开枪吧
Do it.
大量的小程序已经运行
There were a number of applets running.
我们应该能在硬盘上运行
We should be able to run them on our hardware.
我正上传镜像文件给你
I'm uploading a mirror to you now.
你应该收到了吧
You should have it.
这是吉布安的位置吗
You think it's Jibraan?
我不知道  但不管是谁
I can't tell. But whoever it is,
正以30英里的时速在康涅狄格州中南行
They're southbound on Connecticut at 30 miles an hour.
他们刚刚
And they just went
穿过圣马修大教堂
Right through st. Matthew's cathedral
从另一边出来了
And out the other side.
他肯定在地铁上
He's got to be on the metro.
对  红线地铁上
Yes, the Red Line
终点站是华盛顿中心
Ending at Washington Center.
目标是华盛顿中心
Washington Center's the target.
把这些放到车里去
Put these in the car.
杰克  找到吉布安了
Jack, we have Jibraan.
吉布安在地铁上  朝华盛顿中心去了
Jibraan is on the metro, headed toward Washington Center.
克洛伊  我是杰克
Chloe, it's Jack.
我能继续通话了  我们还有多少时间
I'm back on comm. How much time do we have?
不长  他已经到那了
Not long. He's almost there.
听着  托尼必须和吉布安通话
Okay,listen.Tony had to be able to communicate with Jibraan somehow.
看看有没有很强的通信频率
See if they were using some kind of comm frequency
能够在地铁中使用
That was strong enough to work in the subway.
我在找  好了
I'm looking... Okay.
等等
Wait.
有个专有的K频段运行着
There's a proprietary k-band running.
就它了  把我连过去
That's it. Okay. Patch me through.
说吧  杰克
Go ahead, Jack.
吉布安
Jibraan?
吉布安  我是杰克·鲍尔
Jibraan, my name is Jack Bauer.
-能听到我说话吗  -能
- Can you hear me?  - Yes.
你弟弟安全了  我是联邦调查局的
Your brother is safe. I'm working with the FBI.
绑架他的人已经被捕了
The man who was holding him hostage Has been taken into custody.
让我和哈米德说话
Let me talk to Hamid.
他和我们不在一起
He's not with us right now.
不不  我要和他说话
No, no. I need to talk to him.
吉布安  听我说
Jibraan, listen to me.
你弟弟很安全  但你不安全
Your brother is safe, but you are not.
策划这件事的人
The people who are doing this,
给了你一个包裹
They gave you some kind of a package.
不不  他们什么都没给
No, no, no. They didn't give me anything.
这一站  华盛顿中心  是终点站
This stop, Washington Center. This will be the last stop.
我们对车站进行了实时监控
We've got real time coverage of the station.
吉布安  那些人想陷害你恐怖袭击
Jibraan, these people are trying to frame you For a terrorist attack.
他们一定给了你一个包裹
They had to give you some kind of a package.
那一定在车上了
Then it's got to be on the train.
你现在去找一个被遗弃的行李箱
I want you to start looking for an abandoned suitcase,
运动包  背包  之类的
Gym bag, knapsack, anything like that.
我不知道  这里什么都没有
No, I can't tell. There's nothing.
肯定在那里  再找找
It's got to be there. Keep looking.
有个女人
It was a woman.
什么女人
What woman?
哈米德被带走时  他们是一伙的
She was with them when, uh, when they took hamid.
我好像看到她下车
I think maybe I saw her get off the train.
你现在是不是进站了
Are you pulling into the station right now?
你待在车上  等所有乘客下车
Okay, I want you to stay on the train And wait for all the passengers to get off.
是个炸弹  对吧
It's a bomb, isn't it?
是生化武器
It's a biological weapon.
一旦爆炸  会有很多人丧生
If it goes off, a lot of people are going to die.
所有旅客都下车了吗
Are all the passengers off the train?
你看到包裹没
Can you see the package?
没看到
I don't know.
吉布安  继续找
Jibraan, keep looking.
肯定在那里的
It's got to be there.
吉布安
Jibraan?
我看到了
Yes, yes. I see it.
我看到一个防水袋
I see a duffel bag.
打开它
I need you to open it.
等等  为什么是我
Wait. Why me?
为什么我要做这个
Why must I do this?
因为现在  只有你能做到
'Cause right now, you're the only person that can
如果你不做  数以千计的人都会死
And if you don't, thousands of people are going to die.
吉布安  打开包
Jibraan, I need you to open the bag.
我知道我要求的太多
Look, I know I'm asking you a lot.
拜托了
Please.
吉布安  你还在吗
Jibraan, are you still there?
好像是个炸弹
It looks like a bomb.
我看到灯光
I-I see a light.
是个计时器
It's a timer.
正倒计时
It's counting down.
还剩多少时间
How much time is left?
2分10秒
Uh, two minutes, ten seconds.
我们来不及到下面接你了
That's not enough time for us to get down to you.
你试着把东西带到外面来
I want you to try and get the device outside.
在你右手边有自动扶梯
There's an escalator to your right.
现在开始行动
I want you to start moving now.
快啊
Start moving now.
我在路上和你碰面
I'll meet you on the street.
还有一分钟就到了
We're about a minute out.
就是他  停下
That's him. Hold on!
不许动  干嘛这么慌张
Hold on. What's the hurry?
-我必须出去  我必须出去  -那是什么
- I have to get out. I have to get out.  - what is that?
是不是你的
Is that even yours?
我有炸弹
I have a bomb!
炸弹  所有人  退后
This is a bomb. Get back! Everybody, get back!
退后  我有炸弹
Get back! I have a bomb!
等等  他是我们的人  吉布安
Wait, he's with us. Jibraan!
吉布安  我就是和你说话的人
Jibraan. I'm the man who was talking to you.
把罐子给我  跟他们走  他们会帮你
Give me the canister. Go with these men. They'll help you. Go!
他没事吧
Is he all right?
-你是鲍尔先生  -对
- You're mr. Bauer?  - yes.
你做得很好  谢谢你做的一切
You did great. Thank you for everything.
我要见我弟弟
I want to see my brother.
我知道  我们会带他来的
I know. We're going to bring him here.
但现在  你得跟莫伦探员走
But right now, I'd like you to go with agent moran, so he can
做个笔录  拜托了
Take your statement, please.
跟我走
Follow me.
-杰克  -没事没事
- Jack...  - It's all right, it's all right.
你该打一针了
You need to give yourself a shot.
20分钟前打过了  没用
I already did, 20 minutes ago. It's not working.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
我们阻止他们了
We stopped it.
你终于能休息了
You can finally rest.
能给我一张看看吗
Can I have a piece of paper?
当然  这都给你吧
Yeah, sure, you can have all this.
那是什么
What's that?
是第一块版面  我只想要这部分
This is section "a"; it's the only thing I want.
我一看完就给你
I'll give it to you as soon as I'm done.
抱歉  介意我坐下来吗
Excuse me, do you mind if I sit here?
当然不介意
No, of course not.
你是回家吗
You heading home?
我们也是
Us, too.
我们住在格伦代尔
We live in glendale.
我在伍兰岗
Woodland hills.
我老公的父母住那
My husband's parents live there.
你知道普鲁斯尔斯吗
You know the Pelusos?
不知道
I don't think so.
能帮我个忙吗
Do you mind doing me a favor?
好
Sure.
你看到在我们后面那桌的男人吗
Do you see the man behind us at a table?
他穿着西装
He's wearing a suit.
黑色短发
Uh, short, dark hair?
他盯着这里看吗
Yes, is he staring over here?
你认识他吗
You know him?
没有  只是之前他盯着我看
No, it's just that he was staring at me earlier.
你这么漂亮
Well, you're very pretty.
-怎么了  -他走了
- What?  - No, he's moving away now.
她在我视线范围内
I've got her in sight.
她已经在登机口了
She's waiting at the gate now.
他们应该在一小时内登机
They should begin boarding within the hour.
我知道生化武器的威胁已经解除了
Okay, look, I know that the bioweapons threat is over,
但如果你能看着她登机
But I'd feel a lot better if you'd watch over her
我会感觉好些
Until she gets on that plane.
是  长官  她上飞机了我会通知你的
Yes, sir, I'll let you know when she's in the air.
谢谢
Thanks.
我需要你和局办公室联系下
I need you to contact the Bureau office.
告诉他们  我们需要全套审问设备
Tell them we need a full interrogation package
我们回去前要准备好
Ready for when we arrive.
- 是  长官  - 谢谢
- Yes, sir. - Thanks.
杰克?
Jack?
我刚得到消息
I just got word.
乔纳斯·霍奇斯死于汽车炸弹
Jonas Hodges was killed with a car bomb
事发不到一小时
Less than an hour ago.
什么  怎么搞的
What? how?
我们还没什么线索  但可以肯定的是
We don't have any leads yet, but obviously somehow
他那一伙人发现他还活着
The people he was working for found out he was still alive.
也就是说他们也不会放过托尼
That means they're going to be coming after Tony.
我们需要护送他
We need to transport him in a convoy--
动用全部安保武装力量
Full guard detail, weapons ready.
不能再让他遭暗杀了
We're not losing him again. okay.
联邦调查局锁定了阿尔扎利安的位置
The FBI located Al-zarian.
我们无能为力了
There was nothing we could do.
你是说我们丧失了那个毒气罐
You're telling me the canister is gone.
该死
Damn it!
没有那个病原体
Without that pathogen,
我们将前功尽弃
Everything that we've worked for is finished.
你要清楚  托尼被调查局逮捕了
You should also know the FBI has Tony.
那你就该做了他
Then you need to have him eliminated.
-艾伦  -他知道的太多了  卡拉
- Alan. - He knows too much, Cara.
他要是招供出来  我们就玩完了
We can't take the risk that he'll break.
你得把他干掉
You need to take him out.
我跟你讲  那根本没必要
I'm trying to tell you that won't be necessary.
托尼不会被长时间关押
Tony won't be in custody for long.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
相信我
Trust me.
我们另有妙计
We've got another play.
别蒙我
You'd better have.
从波士顿起飞的航班马上就降落了
The incoming flight from Boston will be arriving shortly.
乘客下飞机之后
Once the passengers have deplaned
机场地勤人员会立刻
And the maintenance crew is given a chance
对飞机进行维护和清理
To clean up the aircraft,
之后我们方可登机
We should be able to begin boarding.
感谢您的耐心配合  谢谢
We appreciate your patience. Thank you.
至少  我们知道飞机在半路上了
Well, at least we know the plane's on its way.
眼见为实  耳听为虚
I'll believe that when I see it.
我去弄点咖啡
Well, I'm gonna get some coffee.
你们需要什么吗
Does anybody want anything?
我要杯低咖啡因咖啡
I'll take a decaf.
什么都不需要  谢谢
Nothing for me, thanks.
你确定吗  我请客
Oh, come on. Are you sure? It's my treat.
的确不需要什么  谢谢
No, no, thank you.
好吧
All right.
你老公真是新好男人
Your husband's really nice.
对  他也有对人殷勤的时候
Hmm, he has his moments.
抱歉  我想去一下洗手间
You know what? I'm, I'm gonna use the restroom.
-不介意帮我看一下包吧  -没问题
- Do you mind watching my bag? - Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
直飞西雅图的535次航班
Flight 535, nonstop service to Seattle
现在开始登机了
Is now ready for boarding.
请旅客从17-A登机口登机
All passengers please report to Gate 17-A.
皮尔斯探员
Agent Pierce.
我知道你为我的失态而担忧
I know you're upset I went off protocol,
但我说过  不会有下一次了
But as I told you, it won't happen again.
女士  不会的
No, ma'am, it won't...
不然你就得找别人干这份工作了
Or you'll need to find someone else to do this job.
亚伦  那没必要
Aaron, that won't be necessary.
女士  你说你离开了办公室
Ma'am, you said you left the grounds
去办了件私事
To run a personal errand.
怒我冒昧  您办啥去了
May I ask what it was?
我只是想独自出去
I just needed to get out of here,
清醒下头脑
be alone, clear my head,
一会儿就行
If only for a short time.
今天发生的一切  被劫持为人质
Everything that's happened today-- being held hostage,
乔纳斯·霍奇斯被谋杀
Jonas Hodges' murder...
目睹我虚弱的父亲
And seeing my father so weak and vulnerable...
我快崩溃了
I was feeling overwhelmed.
亚伦  我努力着不辜负我母亲的期望
Aaron, I'm trying to live up to my mother's expectations.
我不希望她
And I didn't want her--
或是相关的任何人
Or anyone else for that matter--
发现我已不堪重负
To know I was being affected by the pressure.
希望你能理解
I hope you can understand that.
是的  女士  我可以理解
Yes, ma'am, I think I can.
你现在感觉好点了吗
You feeling all right now?
确实好点了
I am, actually.
我觉得需要有个人能倾听我的心事
I guess I just needed to tell someone what was going on with me.
很高兴你就是那个我信任的人
I'm glad it was someone I could trust.
您过奖了  女士
Well, thank you, ma'am.
我会即刻准备好那些电话和上网记录
I'll have those phone and internet records
面对来自司法部门的调查员
ready for the justice department investigators shortly.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢  亚伦
Thank you, Aaron.
我是卡宁
This is Kanin.
长官  我是皮尔斯探员
Sir, this is agent Pierce.
希望没打扰您休息
I hope I didn't wake you.
没  皮尔斯探员  我没休息
No, agent Pierce, I'm wide awake.
我能帮你什么
What can I do for you?
卡宁先生  几年前
Mr. Kanin, some years ago,
当我在帕默尔总统身边当保镖时
While I served on president Palmer's detail,
我注意到了一些参谋长办公室规程的变更
I was made aware of some modifications made to the chief of staff's office.
你的意思是在迈克·诺威克的任期中
You mean, during Mike Novick's tenure.
是的  长官  尤其是录音监听系统
Yes, sir, specifically the installation of a voice-activated recording system.
使得联席会议会被录音存档
It allows staff meetings to be logged and archived.
如果你问我是否使用了这套设备
If you're asking whether I used the recording equipment,
回答是  是的我用了
The answer's yes.
长官  当你辞职并离开办公室的时候
Sir, did you disconnect it when you resigned
你关闭了装置吗
And left your office?
没有  怎么了
No. why you asking?
我请求现在暂不回答
I'd prefer not to answer that at this time.
我想知道如何进入数码录音设备
I need to know how to access the digital recorder.
你进不去的  有生物识别锁
You can't. it's secured with a biometric lock.
你需要我的指纹
You need my thumbprint.
亚伦  如果你需要我的帮助
Look, Aaron, if you want my help,
你就先告诉我这是怎么回事
You're gonna have to tell me what this is about.
奥利维亚·泰勒还在使用我的办公室
Olivia Taylor's still using my office.
这和她有什么直接联系吗
Does this have to do with her?
电话里我真的没法讲清楚
I really can't talk about this over the phone right now.
我半小时之内到白宫来
I'll be at the White House within a half hour.
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir.
你不觉得你有些事需要和我说说吗
Do you have something you'd like to say to me?
什么事情
Like what?
我觉得你自己心知肚明
Oh, I think you know.
我不知道
I don't think I do.
不如对我说  "干得好  詹尼斯
How about "good job, Janice,
超便携电脑修复得很好"
on reconstructing the UMPC"?
或者说  "也许我早该想到
Or "just maybe I should have considered the possibility
你确有两把刷子的可能性"
That you actually know what you're doing."
你不了解我
Oh, you don't know me,
如果你了解了  你就会明白
But if you did, you would understand
那是你最后才需要确认的地方
That this is the last place you should look for any type of validation.
你怎么就死不认错呢
How about just acknowledging you were wrong?!
我们准备好出发了
We're almost ready to go.
好  是她吗
Okay. is this her?
是她  但我在首府警局看到她时
Uh, yes, but when I saw her in the Metro,
她戴着黑色假发  穿了件皮衣
she had on this dark wig and a leather jacket.
吉布安  你弟弟到了
Jibraan, your brother's here.
哈米德
Hamid!
我们收拾好走了
Let's pack up.
哈米德
Hamid!
那边那个卖咖啡的地方  借过
Well, the coffee place over here-- excuse me--
没有低咖啡因咖啡
Didn't have decaf,
所以我一直走到那边尽头去了
So I had to go all the way to the other end of the terminal,
总之搞到了
But I want you to know I got it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
我正把链接发到你手机上
I'm sending a link to your phone.
有样东西你需要看一看
It's something I think you should see.
你是谁
Who is this?
打开链接  鲍尔先生
Open the link, Mr. Bauer.
你他妈的是何方神圣
Who the hell is this?
你女儿正在我们的控制之中
Your daughter's in the company of our operatives.
弗兰克斯探员已经上西天了
And agent franks has already been neutralized.
你得帮助托尼·阿尔梅达脱身
You will help Tony Almeida escape
不然我的人会杀了你女儿
Or my people will murder your daughter.
如果你想联系她或者告诉任何人
Any effort to contact her or warn anybody about this
后果是一样的  明白吗
Will have the same result, do you understand?
我做不到你的要求
What you're asking me to do is impossible.
托尼·阿尔梅达已经被看起来了
Tony Almeida's already been secured.
被严密监视着
He's under heavy guard.
那是你的问题
Well, that's your problem.
把这条线连到你耳机上
Put this call on your earpiece
让它一直开着
And keep the line open.
我要监听你说的每句话
I'm gonna be listening to everything you say.
马上行动  鲍尔
Now, Bauer.
你将会为杀害拉里受到应有的惩罚
You're gonna pay for what you did to Larry.
我以为你会跟着莫伦
I thought you were going with moran.
我改了主意
Changed my mind.
我想跟到底
I wanna see this through.
你要尽快把阿尔梅达救出来
You're gonna make your move to break Almeida out soon.
我会告诉你怎么做及何时做
I'm gonna tell you what to do and when to do it.
还有  鲍尔先生
Oh, and mr. Bauer,
如果有其它的探员挡道的话
If any of those agents in that van get in the way,
你要么让他们死  要么让你女儿死
You will have to eliminate them, or your daughter will die.